正确答案就是选项C
The correct answer to this quiz is option C.
如果你找不到答案也没什么
It's okay if you didn't get the answer,
因为有可能这里所包含的内容是我们之前没有学到的
though, because it was covering topics that we haven't learned about yet.
我会在更高的角度为大家解释为什么这个选项是对的或者错的
At a high level I will quickly go through why each option was correct or
而且在接下来的视频里我们会学习到更多的相关内容
incorrect, but we'll learn more about all these terms in the following videos.
我们先来看看这里的是那个选项  找找他们的不同
Let's look at our three options here and look for differences between them.
首先  大家可能注意到了每个方法的里的这个代码
First, you may have noticed that the lines of code inside each method
是一样的
are the same.
这里  这里  和这里
Right here, right here, and right here.
而且代码上面的注释也是一样的
Also the comment above each method is also the same.
这段注释用来描述该方法的功能
And the comment is just what describes what the method does.
这个方法用于根据订单量计算
And the method is supposed to calculate the price of the order
订单的价格
based on the quantity.
另外一个类似的地方在于他们都以private这个词打头
Another similarity is that they all start with the word private.
现在我们还不清楚它的意义  不过这没关系
We don't know what that means yet, but that's okay.
下一个词是这个int
The next word here is int.
虽然在选项B里没有int  但是在选项C里有int
It doesn't say int though in Option B, but it does say int in option C.
所以由于某些原因  这里有些不同
So, for some reason, it's different here.
我们再看下一个部分
Let's move onto the next part.
这里的calculate  price是两个独立的单词
Here it says calculate price and it's two words.
在选项B里  CalculatePrice以驼峰命名法被结合为一个单词
In Option B, CalculatePrice is smushed together as a single word in camel case.
在选项C中也以驼峰命名法结合为一个单词
In option C it's also in camel case, with no spaces.
继续往下我们看到左圆括号和里面的int型数量
Then moving along we see an opening parenthesis and then int quantity.
但是没有右圆括号  这看上去有点奇怪
There's no closing parenthesis though, which is a little weird.
在选项B中  我们可以看到一对圆括号和int型数量
In Option B, we also see opening and closing parentheses and int quantity.
在选项C里  我们同样可以看到一对圆形括号和int型数量
In option C, we see opening closing parentheses, and int quantity.
然后我们看到这里有一对大括号
Then, we see there's an opening brace here, and a closing brace.
但是选项B里没有
But not in option B.
然后在选项C里也有一对大括号
And they do show up in option C, though.
然后我们可以注意到在不同选项的代码里的不同点
So we notice a bunch of differences among the different options.
我们通过Google搜索来看一下什么才是正确的
Let's look at an example of what a valid method should be
方法定义
by doing a Google search.
我打开浏览器搜索“定义Java方法”
So I'm going to open up a browser and then search for define java method.
你也可以用别的关键词搜索
You could have searched for a different query and
也能找到对应的答案
that would have worked as well.
第一个链接看上去不错
This first link looks good.
来自Oracle官方的Java文档
It's from the official Oracle documentation on Java.
点击一下
I'm going to click on it.
如果你之前没看过这个页面  可以暂停视频
If you haven't seen this page before, feel free to pause the video now and
然后点指导纲上的内容了解一下
click on the link in the instructor notes to skim through this page.
虽然这个和我们的代码并不完全一致
While this doesn't match our code exactly, you could try to pattern
大家可以对照着比较一下我们代码的方法声明
match the components of this method declaration with our code.
这里这句话很有用
This other sentence here is helpful.
它说方法声明的必要部分包括方法返回类型
It talks about how the required elements of a method declaration are the method's
方法名称  圆括号和大括号包含的实现体
return type, name, a pair of parenthesis and a body between these braces.
我提到了好多新的词汇  大家可以阅读一下下面的内容
Now, I just mentioned a lot of new words and you can read about them below.
在后面我们会详细介绍更多细节
But, we'll talk about them in more detail later.
我们现在来通过这些信息帮助我们解剖我们这里的选项
Let's try to use this information here to help us narrow down our options.
如果我们用这里的选项和文档页面里正确的代码声明进行对比
If we compare this option with the proper method declaration
这里的这个选项就是不正确的
on the documentation page, this option is actually incorrect.
这里只有左括号没有右括号
There is an opening parentheses here but there's no closing parentheses.
文档里说我们需要一对圆括号
And in the documentation, it says that we need a complete pair of parentheses,
像这里和这里
like right here and right here.
文档里也提到了方法的命名需要和
The documentation also says that a method name has to follow the same rules
对象或者变量的命名方式一致
as the naming for a field or variables, and
也就是我们这里用到的驼峰命名法  里面不包含空格
that means we need to use camel case and not have any spaces in the name.
那么选项A是不对的  我们看看选项B  这里我们缺少了大括号
So it's not option A, let's go on to option B, here we're missing the opening
文件里明确说了需要一对大括号
and closing braces, which the documentation said were required.
选项B没有返回值类型
Option B is also missing the method's return type
而正确的声明方法应该在方法名前有返回类型
which is suppose to come before the method name.
所以这里我们应该有一个int类型
So right here we should have the word int,
因为我们需要这个方法返回价格
because we want to return the price as the output of this method.
选项B不正确有两个原因
So Option B is also incorrect for two reason.
所以希望选项C能好点
So let's hope that Option C is better.
这里我们有一个返回类型
Here we have a return data type which is correct, and
然后我们以驼峰命名法命名方法名称
then we have a method name that is correctly spelled in CamelCase.
而且还有一对圆括号  而且也有
We also have an opening and closing parenthesis, as well as an opening and
一对大括号
closing braces.
这个看上去不错
So this one looks really good.
选项C包含所有方法声明需要的部分
Option C has all the required parts of a method.
接下来我们再深入讲解一下
Let's talk more about this next.